[{"answer": "Whatever", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Bottle-Deposit-Part-1.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Oh.  Oh yeah, I'd be happy to. Uhm, how much d'you want this thing?  I mean, you know, how high are you willing to go", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": " Yes, my friend. I want you to make this project a top priority", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Bottle-Deposit-Part-1.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": " Top priority", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Wait a minute. You mean you get five cents here, and ten cents there. You could round up bottles here and run 'em out to that place for the difference", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Bottle-Deposit-Part-1.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "What d'you mean it doesn't work? You get enough bottles together..", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "No, it doesn't work", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Bottle-Deposit-Part-1.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Yeah, you overload your inventory and you blow your margins on gasoline. Trust me, it doesn't work", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "We have eight", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Bottle-Deposit-Part-1.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Nine thousand dollars", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": " Eleven thousand", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Bottle-Deposit-Part-1.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": " Thirteen thousand", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Twelve thousand", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Bottle-Deposit-Part-1.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Fourteen thousand", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "I really thought you had her there at seventeen thousand", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Bottle-Deposit-Part-1.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Do you hear this clunking", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Well, the shift knob is loose. You know about that", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Bottle-Deposit-Part-1.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": " Have you been picking at it", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "No, I hadn't noticed", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Bottle-Deposit-Part-1.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Have I been picking at it? No. You know. It's just wear and tear", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Yes, well I trust things are moving smoothly. Mr my friend's counting on you, you know", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Bottle-Deposit-Part-1.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": " Get started? I don't understand, my friend", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Well, I was wondering..", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Bottle-Deposit-Part-1.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "Payroll? No, no, I haven't done that", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Assistant to the travelling secretary.  I'm uh, working on the project", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Bottle-Deposit-Part-1.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "Payroll project. my friend? Big uh, big payroll project", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": " Ah, I'm sorry uh, that I doubted you. Whatever you need, just uh, make yourself at home", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Bottle-Deposit-Part-1.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "Yes, he explained it all very clearly", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Hello", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Bottle-Deposit-Part-1.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "Oh, hi", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": " Oh no. What", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Bottle-Deposit-Part-1.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "You left them in the car? How could you leave them in the car", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": " Huh. I don't understand you. It's your own car we're Talking about. You know you wrote the wrong mileage down on the form? You barely know the car. You don't know the mileage, you don't know the tyre pressure. When was the last time you even checked the washer fluid", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Bottle-Deposit-Part-1.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": " The washer fluid is not fine", "qsentId": 34}]